Profits are not made in selling high.
You make the profits in buying cheap.
Mentally prepared already to get
liquidated 10 times.
>> And there's this stats that you know 90%
of people lose money. And you're the
10%. How do you consistently be the 10%.
>> Well, if if I go out and I want to do
day trading, buy sell Bitcoin on a daily
basis, make profits quick. I would be
part of the 90%. For sure. Actually, 98%
or so. My trades [music] where I make
all the money which makes up for the sum
losses I'm doing is the long-term
trades. And it is easy actually. But
money is for me just a number. So I
don't really get attached to it. Which
might be part of this success formula.
It's a little bit of a manipulation of
my own mind. But it works right in the
end. If it prevents you from being
either fearful or greedy, it will set
you apart of most of the people in the
market which are losing money. I put in
500k. If I calculated 10 times, my
maximum downside would be $5 million.
When Bitcoin dumps down and everyone
[music] hates Bitcoin and everyone no
one wants to trade. Everyone lost their
money already. Bitcoin went down already
50 60% that's when I get interested
that's when I open my first trade kind
of small amount if I get liquidated no
problem I open another one I get
liquidated I open it again I open this
trade over and over until I eventually
hit the bottom because we have the money
printers working for us we have the
Federal Reserve the European Central
Bank and [music] we know one thing for
sure that will not just suddenly stop
printing money I do believe in the in
the cycle 4ear cycle might be over
>> the whole crypto the world going wild.
[music] She's the queen of the game.
Stacking crypto like it's her claim to
fame. [music]
Then take a look away.
>> I'm with one of the most wellrespected
and honestly nicest person I've ever
met. Chris from MM Crypto here in Dubai.
>> Thank you very much. You're also very
nice. We met in Miami the first time I
think right at the Micro Sailor Museum
party. There's so many people there.
It's incredible. And I saw you there. I
was like, I need to go say hi. I love
your stuff. And it's crazy how I am here
in Dubai at your really, really
beautiful house. Thank you for having
us.
>> Thank you very much. Happy to have you.
I checked your channel. You are huge in
Taiwan. Uh it's incredible the amount of
views you are getting and it's an honor
for me to be on this channel. A lot of
smart people in your audience. I guess
you have crazy guests. So big. You're
one of the crazy guests.
>> Thank you. Yeah, now it seems like it. I
don't know.
>> I Okay, one thing I really like about
you is how you started and the story. I
think it is so inspiring. Um, would you
just tell some of our audience that
might not have heard it yet from where
you started from how you get here?
>> Yeah, I mean many people who know me,
they will already know. I was driving a
taxi between 2013 and 2017. But while
driving a taxi, I was also studying
economics, right? So in the week I
studied economics. On the weekend I was
driving a taxi to get by, of course, pay
rent, get the get money for food and
stuff. So that was good because I
stopped partying. I started getting more
interested actually in the study I was
doing which was economics. I understood
economics. I understood also the
problems of the current financial
system. We had one professor, he was
working at the European Central Bank
before. So he was a central banker and
he dropped off. He dropped out because
he hated it, right? He hated the
Keynesian economics, the traditional
financial system. So he did a great job
on passing that hatred to us and telling
us what is wrong about the financial
system. So I got a deep understanding
about the problems of the long-term
issues of just printing money, printing
us out of out of problems, right?
Printing us out of out of recessions
because long-term this can't work out. I
knew that already. So I thought this the
solution is silver, the solution is
gold, which is still part of the
solution. But then somewhere around 2017
first I heard about like Bitcoin but I
heard through it through MLMs and I
don't really like MLM so much. Uh
eventually I heard about it not through
LM MLMs like as an investment tool. So I
looked into it with my economic mind and
my taxi driver mind and I understood
okay bitcoin is maybe part of the
solution. So I thought okay there's much
more growth potential. Bitcoin is so
much smaller than gold. So why not put
all my efforts into that? If I know that
the current biggest problem in our life
is the financial system which
redistributes wealth from this poor to
the through the middle class to the
rich, right? And if I know that this
system will collapse at one point, it's
inevitable.
And then the solution will be silver,
gold, and Bitcoin. And Bitcoin has the
biggest growth potential, why not put
all my efforts into that? So, not only
that, I put all my money into it, which
was nothing. I mean, I think the chair
is more expensive than the money I had
back then, but I still it was a little
bit. So, I put all of that money in. Um,
I kept a little bit to just get by. And
then I thought, okay, I need to generate
cash flow because I studied economics. I
studied success mindset and I knew
investment alone will never make you
rich. You need to create a cash flow,
right? So I also tried to find a way to
create a business around this whole
thing and I found YouTube um
sponsorships first affiliate marketing
then I went into trading and I just try
to no matter what create more cash flow
whether it's profits from trades
affiliate marketing YouTube anything
what gets me more cash flow which I can
then put into Bitcoin my primary purpose
financially was always to accumulate as
much Bitcoin as possible possible. Even
if I bought altcoins, it was always for
the purpose to get more Bitcoin.
>> I love that. So, your first Let's go
back to your first YouTube video. Was it
awkward for you? Yes, you want to
generate revenue, but it's so awkward to
just talk to the camera for the first
time.
>> Yeah, it's funny. If people go to the
channel MM Crypto, the main channel, and
you go on videos, and then you sort by
date, you go to the oldest video, you go
to oldest, you will see that video. It's
German, but it's still funny to watch.
Baby, please don't go it. Don't watch
this.
>> Comment
>> cuz it's No, no, no. It was horrible.
That one took me like It's a few
minutes. It took me 8 hours to record. I
had an editor and everything. Was a
friend of mine and um it was it was so
bad. But um I'm still proud of it
because it was the first step into that
world. Um it was fun, right? It's just a
nice example of very uncomfortable
things can lead to something very great
in the end. And right now your trades
are incredible. People are following it
really big numbers too. And people make
shorts about your trade which is another
level. Like usually people talk about
you LA. Yes. But people talk about just
your trade now.
>> Yeah.
>> But earlier off camera you were telling
me how it is actually not as hard as
people think it is, which to me is
mind-blowing.
I I would think that trading is very
difficult for most people and there's
this stats that you know 90% of people
lose money.
>> That's true.
>> Yeah.
>> And you are the 10%. How do you
consistently be the 10%.
>> Well, if I if I go out and I want to do
day trading, buy sell Bitcoin on a daily
basis, make profits quick, I would be
part of the 90% for sure. Actually, 98%
or so. Like let's be honest, it's like
very few people who really
professionally with algo trading or like
they really great traders who put in
more than 10,000 hours into their
trading, they can maybe make some
profits on a small scale, right? Also
not on a big scale. Um but I would be
part of the losing of the losing people.
But I'm I think my trades where I make
all the money which makes up for the sum
losses I'm doing is the long-term
trades. And it is easy actually not the
emotional part that might be difficult
for some people but money is for me just
a number so I don't really get attached
to it which might be part of this
success formula but this very big trade
which is so public and famous is
actually the trade which was the easiest
and I I explained to you before and I
want to do the same thing again. So what
I did in 2022, I did the same also in
2019.
When Bitcoin dumps down and everyone
hates Bitcoin and everyone, no one wants
to trade, everyone lost their money
already. Bitcoin went down already 50
60%, that's when I get interested.
That's when I open my first trade,
right? Kind of small amount. If I get
liquidated, no problem. I open another
one. I get liquidated, I open it again.
I open this trade over and over until I
eventually hit the bottom and I don't
get liquidated like this. You force
actually to eventually hit the bottom.
Like mathematically at one point you
will hit the bottom. That's for sure.
Maybe you get liquidated 10 times. Okay.
But mentally I'm already prepared to get
liquidated 10 times. Much more than that
is actually mathematically impossible
because at one point we hit some number
close to zero. So that will be the
bottom. And once this happens, I have a
position open close to the bottom. Close
enough to the bottom not to get
liquidated. And once that happens, from
that point of time, the market will act
in my favor, will go up. So I'll lean
back and just watch the trade go
profitable. And as we hit cross
resistance levels, I scale up the trade
cautiously, right? The liquidation price
will move a little bit. So I'll be very
cautious with that. I scale it up
cautiously. And that's where we are now.
So, I had this trade which was like a
$30 million trade or so. Uh, it started
as a as a small trade $200,000 I think
at a 10x leverage which was 2 million
and then I scaled it higher and um at
one point when it's very profitable I
start taking profits when we go above
the previous all-time high which was
once we went above $69,000 US which was
the previous all-time high. I start
taking profits right at Fibonacci
extension levels at measured move price
targets and I take 10% 20% and so on.
Now I took 80% profits already. So if
that trade goes all the way down to my
liquidation price which now it was at 50
15,000 or so. Um now the liquidation
price is already at I have to check
maybe 58 59,000.
Possible that we hit that level. Not
very likely but it's very possible. I
mean it's actually if if that is a bare
market it's quite likely because that
would be just a 50% retracement but I'll
be fine because I already took 80%
profits. So now more interesting for the
viewers I want to do the same thing
again. If we do break lower let's say we
break below 82,000 which is at time of
recording the current low. If we break
below that okay I open a new trade let's
say at 79,000 at 10x leverage. If we hit
72,
I get liquidated because it's a 10x. No
problem. I open another one. 65
liquidated. Okay. I open another one. 59
or 50 thou 60,000. I get liquidated. I
open another one again. 55 again. No
matter what, at one point I will hit the
bottom. If not, Bitcoin goes to zero. We
have different problems, I think. Right.
I'll go back to taxi driving maybe.
Hopefully not. Uh but um that that is
the plan right so I'll be fine mentally
prepared already to get liquidated 10
times uh let's say I put in 500k if I
get liquidated 10 times my maximum
downside would be $5 million but
eventually if I do hit the bottom and
Bitcoin hits the new all-time high in
the new next bull market let it be 200
300,000 I don't know what it will be but
I will have made back all this
liquidated money multiple times And I
did that already two times. This will be
the third time. And why am I so certain
that this will happen? Well, because we
have the money printers working for us,
right? You have the Federal Reserve, the
European Central Bank, and we know one
thing for sure. They will not let their
friends down. They will not stop just
suddenly stop printing money. The bigger
the crisis, the more money printing will
happen. And beneficiaries will be of
course things which are not easily
inflatable. Silver, gold, Bitcoin. So I
know time will work in my favor once I
hit the bare bottom with my trade.
That's the strategy.
>> A few takeaways I have I got from what
you just said. First is you believe in
the cycle religiously like you
it seems like you believe in the
four-year cycle religiously.
>> Well not first of all not religiously
but
>> yeah of course I'm sorry not you know
what I mean. [laughter]
>> I'm just joking. I'm joking. Um, but I
do believe in the in the cycle. Fouryear
cycle might be over. Who knows, right? I
mean, we we should have hit the high in
December now or November. That would
have been the real four-ear cycle high.
So, technically, this is already not a
4year cycle. If Bitcoin not suddenly
jumps up to 130,000,
>> the 4-ear cycle is already broken. But I
believe in cycles. So I believe in bare
markets where weekends are shaken out
and then in bull markets where we have
money printing where we have euphoria
exuberance and people just uh
speculating too much. So this will
always happen. We saw that in the stock
market happening over and over again. We
see that everywhere and that's just the
natural state of the market. extreme
fear, extreme greed. And I believe that
this will repeat itself over and over
again. Whether it's going to be fouryear
cycle or not, I don't really care about
that. And because of the money printing,
I believe that new all-time highs will
be higher than the previous all-time
high. By how much? Who knows, right? But
it will be higher. That's what I truly
believe in. And if I'm wrong about that,
well, then law of nature suddenly gets
defeated and uh then I'll get defeated
also and maybe my next trade will not
work out. But
>> so far I am banking on the law of nature
on us having bare markets, bull markets,
on us having extreme fear, extreme
greed. And as long as these laws of
nature continue, I'll be profitable with
my strategy. [snorts]
for
Google.
Else speaking,
Well, I really appreciate that you
answer these questions. I appreciate
your kind words.
Speech analyzer.
Prom
O N B
the other thing that is really important
from what what you said is your crazy
discipline. So, a lot of people add
money to just avoid being liquidated and
then they just lose more and more and
they get deeper and deeper into their
trades.
>> Mhm.
>> And it seems like you don't.
>> That seems very dangerous strategy. It
can help you sometimes, right? But you
have to always put exponentially more in
to move your liquidation price down.
They have to delever, put more margin
in. And if it works, great. If it
doesn't work, you suddenly, let's say
you put $1,000 and you have to move your
liquidation price just three times.
Maybe suddenly you lose 20,000, right?
So I I don't want to focus on that.
Focusing on moving your liquidation
price, not getting liquidated is
focusing on something negative, right?
Preventing something bad to happen. I
rather go in when the bad happens
already. I buy the fear. I buy the the
blood in the streets. It sounds
horrible, right? But you want to buy
cheap, right? And um I think that's what
that's that's how I want to make my
money. So I I want to make my money by
getting in cheap. In real estate, the
people say the same. Your profits are
not made in selling high. You make the
profits in buying cheap, right? And I
want to do the same with my trades. I
want to do the same with my investments.
So whenever I get some fiat in, boom,
Bitcoin. whenever I get profits in. I
mean, even the the 80% I mentioned
earlier, I took in profits on my Bitcoin
trade. It's a Bitcoin settled future,
right? And it's not a US dollar tether
settled future. So, when I take profits,
I take these profits in Bitcoin. If we
go higher, I'm so happy because my hard
asset Bitcoin, which I took the profits
in, they go up with it. If it goes
lower, no problem. Let's say I took a
100 Bitcoin profit. If we go down 50%,
it's still 100 Bitcoin. So that's how I
play with my mind a little bit. So if we
go higher, I'm happy. If we go lower, it
doesn't hurt. It's still the same amount
of Bitcoin. And that's how no matter
what really happens, it doesn't really
freak me out. It's a little bit of a
manipulation of my own mind, but it
works right in the end. If it prevents
you from being either fearful or greedy,
it will set you apart of most of the
people in the market which are losing
money. and they are losing money usually
because they are acting upon their
emotion whether it's fear or greed. So
if you if you can no matter how I do it
with manipulation of my own mind uh
exclude greed and fear from the market
by looking at it just as a number never
trying to never be fearful never be
greedy and I had moments where I was and
I lost money in these moments but if you
can manage that I think you are already
better than most people in the market
and you'll perform well. You know how
when there's like this new shiny meme
coin when it comes out you can be like
I'll put in a little money and maybe a
10x then that's a very quick a mill 2
mill just in what 30 minutes
>> and that is when you lose the money
right because you don't know how the
market is going to move how do you stop
yourself from pressing that buy button
>> well I I know that there's people behind
and they do this to get your Bitcoin
right so in the end they just they just
want you to put it in and they make the
money and they they put it in Bitcoin
like they have they probably have the
same goal to just accumulate more of
what's valuable but they don't really
believe in their their their meme coins.
You see that now I was for a long time
now already just promoting only Bitcoin
because if you look at how the market is
structured now you have millions of
altcoins right with Solana like everyone
can easily make an altcoin not just meme
coins even these smart contract
platforms which seem to solve some
problem maybe or serve some purpose just
make the math we have whatever like 200
million people who got in touch with
crypto already maybe 300 00 million
people they got at least in touch with
crypto almost everyone in Turkey already
got in touch with crypto for example so
let's say it's 200 million we have 8
billion people that is like maybe 40x
but then we have a lot of people and
there's no offense but like purchasing
power-wise there's a lot of people which
can't add so much purchasing power to
crypto anymore like many people in India
or Africa so
amazing human beings but purchasing
power wise not so much more can flow
into it. A lot of smart money, a lot of
big money is already invested and has
already easy access to crypto through
things like Black Rockck and so on. So
the amount of purchasing power which can
still come into the space is quite
limited, right?
Let let it be like I don't know if
5x 10 x 20x okay that that's possible
but look at the amount of new projects
hitting the market we have like
2017 we had a thousand altcoins maybe
2020 already it was 20 30,000 now we
have millions so it is impossible that
the additional purchasing power hitting
the market can serve all of these
additional altcoins being in the market.
So, it is impossible for all of these
altcoins to go up. Mathematically, it
makes much more sense for me to go to
the first mover advantage to go to
Bitcoin winner takes it all principle
rather than trying to hit this one BNB
maybe which has value which can still
grow. It's very difficult to find this
one needle in the haststack. Right? So
instead of like making all of that
research, having sleepless sleepless
nights, I rather stick with a winner,
stick with Bitcoin. And honestly,
Bitcoin is at 90,000 now. I think the
best case scenario, let it be $10
million per Bitcoin, even if that's far
out in the future, that's 100x. So I
rather take a potential 100x maybe worst
case in my opinion a 10x rather than
some alcon which might do 100x maybe but
most likely it's going to go minus 100%.
Or if it goes minus 99% you have to make
a 100x to get your money back. So I I I
just don't play that game. I think risk
return-wise, if you look at the
probability function, risk return-wise,
the best bet even for small people is
Bitcoin.
>> And life is so much more than just the
trades.
>> Yes,
>> the world is so beautiful. Go out and
enjoy life, spend time with your
friends, your family, and people are so
trapped in the numbers game, but they
forget the only thing that is limited.
Of course, Bitcoin is limited, but your
time and your health is also also very
limited. And you're now also very
focused on your new channel that is
talking about health and I I'm just
intrigued how how did that transition
come about?
>> Mm. Health. Yeah, I think health is
amazing. I it's it's such an important
part of our life. Before I was focusing
on crypto, on money because I wanted to
myself wanted to make more money of
course and I thought okay the best thing
is to add as much value as possible to
the people so you can get as much reach
as possible and then convert that reach
that attention into money. Right? That
was the strategy. Now I feel like okay I
achieved a lot of um monetary wealth
already. A lot of my early followers
achieved a lot of monetary wealth. I
experienced myself how important it is
to be healthy also. So I want to apply
the exact same principle to health now.
Right? And eventually if I can help a
100 million people to get more healthy
or a billion people to get more healthy
that will translate in a lot of wealth
also. But the more health I create in
the world the more money I can make from
it. That's a beautiful thought process.
I thought so my goal will be to reach as
many people as possible with my channel
MM Health and the more people I reach if
I can monetize that somehow by adding
value to people by teaching them about
health
make more money by creating more health
I thought that is uh even more beautiful
than the the crypto thing right
>> so it's like sound money and also
healthy lifestyle okay tell me one
mistake that you've made in the past on
health that if you could go back and
tell yourself stop doing that, what
would that one advice be?
>> Yeah. I don't want your channel to be
taken down, but that would definitely be
not doing a root canal treatment.
>> Really?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I I had a root canal
treatment and uh there there's a big
conspiracy behind I don't want to get
too deep into it, but it seems like root
canals can be very problematic for
humans.
>> But we're going to check out your stuff.
I'm I'm sure you're going to talk about
it.
>> I will publish a video about that very
soon. I have to make sure that I do it
in a politically correct manner that the
video can stay online but I will
definitely make a video about that.
There's also a huge documentary root
cause which people can watch. It's very
great after watching it I took this
tooth out. So that that is one message I
want to give out to the people because I
know many people have these root canal
treatments.
>> I was expecting something like
lightweight don't drink or don't smoke
but this is wow this is deep and you dig
dig really really deep.
>> Exactly. I think they heard this don't
drink don't smoke many times and that is
still correct don't drink don't smoke
but that is a more special thing I
wanted to share with you guys because
you would never believe
>> what are the little things that make you
happy nowadays other than I think for
for all your viewers to grow wealthier
and healthier what are the little things
in life that makes you smile
>> yeah that's a great question I mean many
people watching that I think you have a
very smart audience very financially
educated audience. So your focus is
already on money. Great. But I think
there are many things which are
important in life and many things which
are important for us to be happy long
term. And yes, that might be wealth. But
not just wealth as striving for it,
wanting more cars and stuff. Having
wealth as a tool to set you free, right?
Or as a tool to be able to pay for an
operation for your family or something
that really makes you happy. So then you
can spin it further and you can say okay
health is very important life is very
important purpose is important for me
personally I I found out that faith is
very important these more
non-materialistic things they really
make you happy I think and then of
course having a purpose which can be
raising your kids it can be growing a
value adding company it can be growth in
general it can be working on your health
or anything educating people
a purpose in general is I think is very
important. Um I like creating wealth but
for me wealth money making money is just
like a scorecard. So it's for me like a
scorecard and showing how successful I
am in what I'm doing. And if success
then is for me a measurement of how many
people I can help then that is a great
way of of course creating happiness
through money right but other than that
I think things like health purpose
family these things are long-term much
much more important to focus on.
>> You know this is very wholesome talking
to you. It's like you have this very
like calm energy that I think most
people do not really understand because
the crypto market is so crazy and they
assume people in it are just ups and
downs. But you have this energy that
calms people down and I really
appreciate this conversation we have.
Please come back soon and thank you for
having me here.
>> Thank you for having me here. Right. I'm
I'm I'm I'm very grateful to be here and
to talk to this audience. Um so I want
to come to China and Taiwan at any point
in the future. Big pleasure to be here.
Thank you very much. And you said the
calmness. It's true. But some of my
emergency videos don't spread so much
calmness. I don't know if you saw them.
>> The thumbnails. That's what I want.
That's what I'm trying to communicate.
like yes that
>> but you have this calm energy that I
would love people to just
>> absorb.
>> Thank you very much.
Thank you.